University Library - Record Group 13 WLU.RG.0013
Washington and Lee University, University Library Special Collections and Archives
University Library - Record Group 13
Date Not Yet Determined
Washington and Lee University, University Library Special Collections and Archives
WLU.RG.0013
x Linear Feet
Online Access
View materials from the collection online via W&L's Digital Archive
Scope and Contents
This record group contains materials created by the University Library during the course of its regular business, such as official publications and records about its management.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research use.
- James Graham Leyburn Library
  - Box 52a, 1970-1990; .5 Linear Feet
    Scope and Contents
    This box contains correspondence, Alumni Magazine issues, photographs, 'The Big Move' materials, and a copied 1876 map of Washington and Lee University with proposed changes.
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Materials received from the administration of Maurice D. Leech.
  - Library Publications
    - Library Letters, Vol. 1, no. 1 (Jan. 2005)- Vol. 8, no.2 (Win. 2012)
    - Annual Library Report, 1979-
    - Handbook of the University Library, 1979-
  - Friends of the Library
    - FOLios, 2006-
- Cyrus Hall McCormick Library
  - Report of the Friends of the Cyrus Hall McCormick Library, 1951-1968; 1 Box
  - Handbook of the University Library, 1939-1978
  - Annual Library Report, 1968/1969-1978/1979
  - Guide to the Manuscript Collections, 1976